var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَثِيمٍ",
        "answer": "sinful",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "athīmin",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرَائِكِ",
        "answer": "thrones",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-arāiki",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرَائِكِ",
        "answer": "the thrones",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-arāiki",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "555",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1401",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1402",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) what",
        "pcklId": "1403",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1404",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1405",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1406",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "731",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "546",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed ",
        "pcklId": "547",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their people",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "ahlihimu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the former (people)",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتُنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "āyātunā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَبْرَارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the righteous",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-abrāri",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَبْرَارَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-abrāra",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَبْعُوثُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) resurrected",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "mabʿūthūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُتْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "are recited",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "tut'lā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُوِّبَ",
        "answer": "been rewarded",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thuwwiba",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(in) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَمُوا",
        "answer": "committed crimes",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ajramū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَحْجُوبُونَ",
        "answer": "surely will be partitioned",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "lamaḥjūbūna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَافِظِينَ",
        "answer": "(as) guardians",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ḥāfiẓīna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِتَامُهُ",
        "answer": "Its seal",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "khitāmuhu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَخْتُومٍ",
        "answer": "sealed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "makhtūmin",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they give less",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yukh'sirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرَاكَ",
        "answer": "can make you know",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "adrāka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرَاكَ",
        "answer": "can make you know",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "adrāka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Judgment",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَوْهُمْ",
        "answer": "they saw them",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "ra-awhum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّ",
        "answer": "before (the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "937",
        "tlit": "lirabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "938",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيقٍ",
        "answer": "a pure wine",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "raḥīqin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرْسِلُوا",
        "answer": "they had been sent",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "ur'silū",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْقُومٌ",
        "answer": "written",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "marqūmun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْقُومٌ",
        "answer": "written",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "marqūmun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَانَ",
        "answer": "(the) stain has covered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rāna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِجِّينٍ",
        "answer": "Sijjin",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sijjīnin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِجِّينٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Sijjin",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "sijjīnun",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَاطِيرُ",
        "answer": "Stories",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "asāṭīru",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْقَوْنَ",
        "answer": "They will be given to drink",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yus'qawna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْنِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Tasneem",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tasnīmin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْرَبُ",
        "answer": "will drink",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yashrabu",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْهَدُهُ",
        "answer": "Witness it",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yashhaduhu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَصَالُو",
        "answer": "(surely) will burn",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "laṣālū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضْحَكُونَ",
        "answer": "laugh",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaḍḥakūna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضْحَكُونَ",
        "answer": "they will laugh",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaḍḥakūna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَضَالُّونَ",
        "answer": "surely have gone astray",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "laḍāllūna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُطَفِّفِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who give less",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lil'muṭaffifīna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظُنُّ",
        "answer": "think",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yaẓunnu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْتَدٍ",
        "answer": "transgressor",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "muʿ'tadin",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْرِفُ",
        "answer": "You will recognize",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "taʿrifu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Great",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "548",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلِّيِّينَ",
        "answer": "Illiyin",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ʿilliyyīna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلِّيُّونَ",
        "answer": "(is) Illiyun",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ʿilliyyūna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنًا",
        "answer": "A spring",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ʿaynan",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَغَامَزُونَ",
        "answer": "they winked at one another",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yataghāmazūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُجَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the wicked",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-fujāri",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "yafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكِهِينَ",
        "answer": "jesting",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fakihīna",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَرَّبُونَ",
        "answer": "those brought near",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-muqarabūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَرَّبُونَ",
        "answer": "those brought near",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-muqarabūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْقَلَبُوا",
        "answer": "they returned",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "inqalabū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْقَلَبُوا",
        "answer": "they would return",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "inqalabū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he says",
        "pcklId": "1605",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَالُ",
        "answer": "it will be said",
        "pcklId": "1606",
        "tlit": "yuqālu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "1607",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُومُ",
        "answer": "will stand",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yaqūmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) record",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "A book",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "kitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) record",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "A book",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "kitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "yukadhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "can deny",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "yukadhibu",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "tukadhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "to the deniers",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "lil'mukadhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارِ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "l-kufāri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارُ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "l-kufāru",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1345",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "1346",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "used to",
        "pcklId": "1347",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1348",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "they give by measure (to) them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kālūhum",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكْتَالُوا",
        "answer": "they take a measure",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ik'tālū",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرُّوا",
        "answer": "they passed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "marrū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمِزَاجُهُ",
        "answer": "And its mixture",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wamizājuhu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِسْكٌ",
        "answer": "(will be of) musk",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "mis'kun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَضْرَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) radiance",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "naḍrata",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "observing",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "observing",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعِيمٍ",
        "answer": "bliss",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "naʿīmin",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّعِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) bliss",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "l-naʿīmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَتَنَافَسِ",
        "answer": "let aspire",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "falyatanāfasi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَنَافِسُونَ",
        "answer": "the aspirers",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "l-mutanāfisūna",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their faces",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "wujūhihim",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَنُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "they weigh (for) them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wazanūhum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوْفُونَ",
        "answer": "they take in full",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yastawfūna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "For a Day",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "liyawmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "biyawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "So today",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "fal-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "83",
        "ayah": "34"
    }
]; 
export default words;